Caleb, how we doing?
I'm doing good. How are you doing?
Awesome, man. Hey, listen, we just made
a trade, all right? So,
we are we're going to make you our first
round pick, man. Congratulations.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much. I appreciate
it.
Caleb, how are you, man? It's Coach
Vrabel.
I'm doing good, Coach. How are you
doing?
Doing great, man. Congratulations. We're
excited to have you.
Um
I hope you're with Yep, I hope you're
with your family and
you're enjoying this and we can't wait
to get you here and [music]
give you a chance to to help the
football team, man. Can't wait to get
there. Thank you, Coach. Okay, here's
here's Mr. Kraft, Caleb.
Caleb, how's it going?
Welcome to the Patriots. The New England
Patriots select Caleb Lomu,
tackle, Utah.
Right now,
>> [cheering]
>> every tackle and interior offensive
lineman I had in my top 50 are off the
board through 28 picks. Good job, boys.
>> [applause]